testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Did everyone go watch it?
I don't like my hair right now.
I just watched it too.
On TV.
But seriously at Gag Concert
the seniors we worked with
this time
are totally
from
our era
like really
really
famous and popular
comedians you know.
Seeing them in person like this
made me so
nervous
and shaky.
I was so touched
because they treated us so well.
They treated us
so warmly
so all I could think about was working hard.
I can't believe I went on Gag Concert
would young Baek Jiheon know about this?
Ah but it was so funny.
It was honestly even funnier going there in person guys.
It was really so funny.
Why?
Why? But how did we suddenly
reach 57th place?
I really
can't believe it.
No but why why is that?
Why?
Suddenly
did Inkigayo play a big role today?
What is it?
Our Flovers
really worked
hard
for us.
Actually I
didn't talk with the Unnies
about this yesterday.
I didn't talk with the Unnies about it.
I just thought about it by myself.
Ah what should we do
for our song this time
to be heard
by many people?
Our Flovers
or maybe
should we even
bet wearing short skirts? Kind of
I had these kinds of thoughts.
That re-performance
re-stage
where our Jiwon
tore it up
I wondered if we should do something like that
so if we're 57th
and we reach
top 50 doing something like that seems too dangerous
But
I can't do it alone guys I haven't even talked to the members yet
If this
goes up on Shorts later
the members might say to me
like
hey Baek Jiheon
what
is this
they could say that
I don't want that
Pit-a-pat
Performing Pit-a-pat
This much
Ah why are there so many Flovers who like Pit-a-pat?
Pit-a-pat
Why why why is that?
Why do you like it?
What is it?
I need to study
you like it when I say things like this.
My
mom says things like that
but to talk about my mom
I'm way too
old now
from being 15
or 16
I'm 24 now
but try it once anyway
once
But
someday
I think I'll do it.
I should do
Pit-a-pat if Flovers want it this much someday
at a
fan meeting.
Rather than a concert
today
a bit
how should I put it?
Ah
right.
Today's Inkigayo?
Wait what was I trying to say? I guess I am
a little bit tired.
Even I don't really know what I'm saying. The topic is bouncing around a bit right.
Ah still I slept quite a bit today catching up on sleep.
Very tired
Actually I'm not sleepy right now.
My mind
might be
sleepy but my eyes are perfectly fine right now.
Perfectly fine.
Today
I slept for 3
or 4 hours at least
today's
makeup
was Ariel.
Not right now but earlier
for the music show
Ah but wait
while watching Gag Concert
and coming back
our
challenge
was uploaded there
the
Reels
with Leeseo
the challenge I filmed with Leeseo was uploaded.
I feel so good.
Finally I can
tell you that I'm close
with Leeseo.
I don't know what Leeseo thinks but
I think we're close.
We go to the same salon so we're close
uh
she's so
cute
so cute.
So we actually
matched our outfit colors too. In white.
We matched in white.
We've actually went on
quite a few dates too.
We've hung out
a lot more
than
you guys think.
It'd be nice if our music show schedules overlapped later.
Right. I like cute people. I like
kind babies. Kind people.
Ah
anyway
I'm so happy
to be able to show you
the jewel from my jewel box.
Hmm.
Cheese Challenge. Cheese
Cheese
It's delicious.
Cheesy.
Hmm.
Yeah
Hmm
Cheesy
Do you know how we ended up filming that challenge?
We were done
so
after M Countdown
was over
I was about to go home
but
the challenge
popped up on Instagram. So I thought
should I
film this today?
I like
my hair makeup
and outfit today
and I dressed pretty nicely today so should I film it before I go?
So
I
asked the staff Unnies
to get ready
and asked them
if they could
play the song next to me
but everyone
came to watch.
The staff Unnies
closed the door
just to watch
from the side.
So I said oh I was going to film this alone this is a bit pressuring.
Are you feeling pressured? Should I leave? Ah that's not it either but
just
don't make fun of me.
So the staff members were all watching next to me and the staff Unnies
I
filmed this
really hard
from learning it at first
with the staff
Unnies.
The result of my talent show. Kind of really
But
it was filmed a bit from the side.
They apologized to me.
Isn't tomorrow Chaewon's different one?
Chaewon's is probably a different one.
Mine is kind of an experiment tomorrow.
Cheeky
Days of Challenge
You want me to wipe the lens?
Done right?
It got a bit cleaner right?
Ah you meant pretend to wipe it. No
do it again.
I can't
What do I do.
do it again.
I saw
Chaewon and she kind of
did it like this.
It doesn't suit me.
Chaewon Unnie pulls it off so well though.
Rub rub
Kind of this vibe.
Mmhmm.
Die of day show
I seriously thought about filming this a long time ago
but I haven't yet. I thought about filming the gee gee gee gee challenge a long time ago too
but only filmed it now
Die
Ppooi show
Ddoo-i-na
Oh
I've been asking
Hayoung Unnie and Jiwon Unnie to film this for me
since Ulsan but
we ended up doing it
at Weverse Con.
What was it
what was it again
what else did I do recently
What are
the trending
challenges?
Bad
Ah I really can't do this one.
This one
really doesn't suit me at all
so I feel like it's pretty much doing a challenge for a song that doesn't fit me.
You say I don't look bad at all.
Guess I'm good.
At my house
there's a fire?
Isn't it kind of like this?
Actor waiting
day 1.
At my house
there's a fire?
What else is there? What else?
Red red
Toad
Is it this?
It's hard.
Catch catch
Actually
I filmed it once
but it was so
bad that I didn't post it.
I think I filmed it in Japan.
No.
What was it?
I should watch it once
Red
riding
isn't it acting surprised like this?
But this
Chaewon did it so
well
that I wouldn't
dare copy it.
You want me to do Girls' Generation.
Don't make
fun of me
for being young.
It's just a passing
conversation.
No
don't make fun of me
for being young
I don't really know it.
Why are you laughing?
Don't laugh.
I said don't laugh.
If I learn it properly
I can do well
it's just because I don't know it right now.
I vaguely
remember seeing it
but I can't remember the exact dance moves.
How do I do this? Anyway doing this
Don't laugh
and
I think there was something like this
What is this? I don't know.
Isn't it something like this?
I'm good at it when I do it.
I can hear it.
Ah it turns off.
If I get a call in the middle.
I told my mom
I'm doing a live. She said
she put the laundry
in the dryer so I should take it out
and sort it.
Today my mom and dad are truly
the MVPs.
I really respect
my mom and dad.
It wasn't my mom?
It wasn't my mom but if it wasn't for my dad I really couldn't have done that hair today.
I would have gone out with the exact same hair.
Boringly
right?
No but this is all
because of my mom and dad. They slept in the living room.
If they sleep in the living room I can't turn on the lights when I go out there right.
Right?
So I just brought my bag
but my hair pieces
weren't in my bag.
The pieces were next to the bag. I couldn't see them
because it was so dark.
So that's all
because of my mom and dad.
I told my mom and dad I love them.
And thanked them.
Man today
I was talking with the staff Unnies
and when filming
the gee gee challenge
the staff Unnies were saying
it has to be a thumbnail
where my waist looks good.
Like that
so
I heard that and said
the culprits were right here.
What?
The culprits
were inside.
Huh?
Got caught red-handed.
Is there anything else you want to see?
But I've done this one too much.
How is it?
This kind of vibe.
I only know up to here.
Still I know quite a lot right.
Because recently I've
looked up a lot.
Since idols
like Kiss of Life
or
ITZY
all
film so many challenges
I
did some research
on what kind of challenges
girl groups
film a lot.
But
on my algorithm
usually
there wasn't much
besides clothes
and stuff like that normally.
But as for "Someone will return from prison"
I really
don't know what that is.
I know it's a meme by now but I still haven't seen it.
From prison
why
would
a criminal
return?
We're really 53rd.
Crazy.
Flovers what's going on?
Wow.
You guys are kind of amazing.
Yeah
Flover
you're the best.
Short hair
I liked long hair
until recently
but suddenly
I want to have long hair.
Long hair
I caught
the long hair disease
I want long hair.
Short hair
has passed.
Among next week's
outfits should I spoil
my favorite outfit beforehand?
Maybe
probably
Music Core
No.
For M Countdown
I think Flovers will like it.
Anyway my guess
is that for M Countdown
Flovers will like it.
Music Bank
Music Bank is pretty too.
But
for me Music Core.
We really have a lot of content out this time right.
It's really
fun to watch isn't it?
Our
staff members
really worked hard for it.
Also
what else is there?
Anything worth talking about?
I'm starting to get a little sleepy now.
Wow
I just
almost
almost dozed off.
But I don't want to sleep.
I said I don't want to sleep.
But I think I'm too
sleepy.
It's still a waste of time.
This time is such a waste.
Ah this
time is precious.
That can happen right.
But I should sleep.
Since I haven't even washed up yet.
The broadcast
I'll go to sleep
now then.
Thank you guys for hanging out with me like this while I'm talking nonsense
I was a bit
bored since my mom and dad left
and
I was constantly
with the members
all week
but suddenly
got some time to sleep alone.
So I was a bit
bored.
Thank you
Flover
I'll work harder
on stage next week. Today with the members
most of the members didn't even sleep
for two hours
With the Unnies
after pre-recording we went
to the cafeteria
together
and talked about what we should do
and gave feedback
on the stage
and stuff
we really shared a lot of those conversations so
I think I can do
even better next week.
Anyway I
didn't yawn.
Anyway I'll
go now.